<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<xt:extensions xmlns:xt="http://www.oxygenxml.com/ns/extension"
    xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
    xsi:schemaLocation="http://www.oxygenxml.com/ns/extension http://www.oxygenxml.com/ns/extension/extensions.xsd">
    <xt:extension id="com.oxygenxml.startml.Framework">
        <xt:location href="startml.zip"/>
        <xt:version>1.0.0</xt:version>
        <xt:oxy_version>15.1+</xt:oxy_version>
        <xt:type>framework</xt:type>
        <xt:author>George Bina</xt:author>
        <xt:name>StratML oXygen framework</xt:name>
        <xt:description xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml">
            <h1>StratML oXygen framework</h1>
            <p>This addon adds StratML support to oXygen. This includes new file templates, 
                automatic schema validation, visual interface for authoring StartML documents,
                XML Catalog and transformation scenarios to convert StratML to HTML.</p>
        </xt:description>
        <xt:license>
<![CDATA[

END USER LICENSE AGREEMENT
Copyright 2013 Syncro Soft SRL, Romania. All rights reserved.

Redistribution and use in source and binary forms, with or without modification, are
permitted provided that the following conditions are met:

1. Redistributions of source code must retain the above copyright notice, this list of
conditions and the following disclaimer.

2. Redistributions in binary form must reproduce the above copyright notice, this list
of conditions and the following disclaimer in the documentation and/or other materials
provided with the distribution.

THIS SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED BY Syncro Soft SRL ''AS IS'' AND ANY EXPRESS OR IMPLIED
WARRANTIES, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, THE IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY AND
FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE ARE DISCLAIMED. IN NO EVENT SHALL Syncro Soft SRL OR
CONTRIBUTORS BE LIABLE FOR ANY DIRECT, INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL, SPECIAL, EXEMPLARY, OR
CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES (INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, PROCUREMENT OF SUBSTITUTE GOODS OR
SERVICES; LOSS OF USE, DATA, OR PROFITS; OR BUSINESS INTERRUPTION) HOWEVER CAUSED AND ON
ANY THEORY OF LIABILITY, WHETHER IN CONTRACT, STRICT LIABILITY, OR TORT (INCLUDING
NEGLIGENCE OR OTHERWISE) ARISING IN ANY WAY OUT OF THE USE OF THIS SOFTWARE, EVEN IF
ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGE.

THIRD-PARTY LIBRARIES AND RESOURCES
Third party libraries and resources redistributed in this package are subject to their 
respective licenses.



]]></xt:license>
    </xt:extension>
</xt:extensions>
